{
  "title": "Assessment: States of Matter",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What state of matter has a definite shape, size, and volume?",
      "choices": ["Solid", "Liquid", "Gas", "Air"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What solid will break into pieces when dropped?",
      "choices": ["Paper", "Glass", "Steel", "Eraser"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What state of matter has a definite volume and can flow?",
      "choices": ["Solid", "Liquid", "Gas", "Air"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most common liquid?",
      "choices": ["Medicine", "Shampoo", "Juice", "Water"],
      "correctAnswer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What state of matter can expand and flow?",
      "choices": ["Solid", "Liquid", "Gas", "Air"],
      "correctAnswer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the gas that people and animals breathe out?",
      "choices": ["Carbon Dioxide", "Oxygen", "Helium", "LPG"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Steel is used for making many sharp objects.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Drink liquids without carefully checking if it's safe.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Tell an adult if you smell gas near an LPG tank.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Never take any medicine without the supervision of an adult.",
      "choices": ["True", "False"],
      "correctAnswer": 0
    }
  ]
}
